# CHIZA BARBER

#### (832) 754-6556

chiza.barber@gmail.com www.chizabarber.com

### **About Me**

I call myself an "office veteran". My experience in administrative roles spans more than a decade across various industries. Now, I'm hoping to expand my skillset in the tech field.

As a self-starter, I enjoy creative work environments where team synergy is balanced with a good level of individual autonomy.

# **Experience**

Six Foot Staffing • 2018-2019 Administrator / Webmaster

Six Foot Games • 2017-2018 Customer Support Agent

Houston Swim Club • 2007-2017 Administrative Staff

WT Café Sugar Land • 2013-2015 Operations Manager

### **Education**

DigitalCrafts Houston • 2019 Full-Stack Flex Program

Houston Community College • 2011
Associate in Arts

#### **Skills**

Office Administration • Customer Support / Service

Record-keeping, document management, billing and invoicing, customer support via phone and email, performance metrics, team processes and collaboration tools

Web Development • Website Administration

Full-stack web app and site development, Wordpress and Squarespace administration and blogging, social media management on Facebook, LinkedIn and Twitter.

### **Tools**

Microsoft Office, Google Apps and various CRM and ATS systems

Atlassian JIRA and Confluence, Trello, Podio and GitHub

Wordpress and Squarespace CMS administration and blogging

Buffer and HootSuite social media management tools

Visual Studio Code, Atom and SublimeText code editors